tutor.com 2019-04-26

# Privacy Policy - Tutor.com

Effective Date: April 6, 2018

This Privacy Policy governs your use of the websites located at [ www.princetonreview.com](https://www.princetonreview.com/) and at [www.tutor.com](https://www.tutor.com/) and other websites and mobile applications on which TPR Education, LLC d/b/a The Princeton Review, Tutor.com, Inc., or one of their affiliates (collectively, “we” or “us”) posts this Privacy Policy (collectively “Sites”).

This Privacy Policy outlines the type of Personal Information and other information that is collected through the Site and how that information is used. We take your privacy seriously, and we have implemented security measures to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, use, and modification.

### Your Consent to this Privacy Policy

By visiting this Site or using the products or services offered on or through this Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into the Terms of Use for this Site. By providing Personal Information to this Site, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories, in accordance with applicable law.

### Personal Information

We may from time to time ask you for Personal Information, and we may collect certain information from your device each time you visit our Site. We may also receive Personal Information from third parties with whom we have a business relationship, including our organizational customers, resellers, licensees, and franchisees. “Personal Information” means personally identifiable information and includes, for example, your name; street address; e-mail address; SMS or text message address; phone number; credit card and other payment information; information regarding your academic and extracurricular activities and interests that may identify you; and other information that may identify you as an individual or allow online contact with you.

You may review and correct the Personal Information that is accessible to you under the settings for your account on our Site or by calling 800-2REVIEW.

#### FOR PARENTS OF CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13:

For any user under the age of 13, we must have permission from such user’s parent or legal guardian before we collect or use any Personal Information of such user on the Site. You are welcome to call us at 800-2REVIEW to review any Personal Information we have collected about your child. You may request that we delete this information or specify that we collect no more of your child’s information. We will need to verify the identity of anyone requesting information about a child under the age of 13 to ensure that the person is in fact the child’s parent or legal guardian.

### Right to Opt In and Opt Out

You have the right to “opt in” and “opt out” of certain uses of your Personal Information by us. For example, you may elect not to receive promotional correspondence from us. You may make this request under the settings for your account by indicating which correspondence you would like to receive.

You can also send an e-mail to prep@review.com. In this e-mail, please say whether: (i) you would like to opt out of receiving all e-mail promotional correspondence from us in general or (ii) if you would only like to opt out of certain of our e-newsletters or correspondence and if so which ones or (iii) you would like to opt out of receiving SMS or text messages. You may also opt out of our promotional e-mails by clicking on an opt-out link within the e-mail you receive.

Please understand that if you opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us.

We do not disclose your Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes except as described under “SCHOOLS WHICH ARE INTERESTED IN YOU” or “LICENSEES AND FRANCHISEES” below.

We may allow our affiliates and third parties, including advertising companies and ad networks, to display advertisements on our Site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. These third parties may collect information about whether you, or others who are using your device, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver (such as click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, etc.), and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. Some of these third party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies and provides information about this behavioral advertising practice ([www.networkadvertising.org](https://www.networkadvertising.org/)). You may opt out of our collection of data for use by third party ad companies to provide targeted advertising to you of our products as you visit other sites. Cookies are unique to each device. Therefore, you must opt out separately on all devices you use. If you delete all of your cookies (specifically, the “Opt-Out” cookie), you will have to go through the opt-out process again to reactivate your opted-out status.

### Information Collected on this Site

#### USER-PROVIDED INFORMATION

We may collect Personal Information from users when they register or create an account on our Site, or through other ways such as through such user's activities, transactions and completion of surveys or other similar types of canvassing and other online forms on our Site. We may also obtain the date, time and content of messages in the course of your use of our products or services as well as any transcripts or content provided during real-time or asynchronous tutoring sessions. You may provide this information directly to us or consent to us receiving it from a third party (such as Facebook). We may use or disclose information provided by users in response to surveys or similar types of canvassing tools for purposes of promotions or other statements to third parties in a manner that does not personally identify any individual user. If you provide us email addresses and other information of your friends and/or family members for us to send information about our products and services, we will maintain such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

#### SITE USAGE INFORMATION

  * Cookies. We and our service providers may use “cookies” to keep, and sometimes track, information about you, and to create a personalized web experience. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your device’s web browser. Cookies track where you travel on our Site and what you look at and purchase. By using this Site, you agree to the use of cookies in this way. Most web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. Additionally, if you have a Flash player installed on your device, your Flash player can be set to reject or delete Flash cookies. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Site or certain areas or features of the Site.
  * Clear GIFs. We and our service providers may use “clear GIFs” (a/k/a “Web beacons” or “pixel tags”) or similar technologies, on the Site and/or in our communications (e.g., in our HTML-based e-mails) which enable us to know whether you have visited a Web page or received or opened a message. This allows us to know the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.
  * IP Address and Clickstream Data. We automatically collect information from your browser when you visit our Site. This information includes your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us and the referring website address.

### How Personal Information is Used

We may use your Personal Information to:

  * provide you with and personalize our products and services, including storing transcripts of, and content provided during, on-demand tutoring sessions or online classroom sessions, creating an account for you, and enrolling you in free trials;
  * process your orders, manage your account, provide you customer service, and ask for your feedback and send you surveys to help make our products and services better;
  * maintain our internal records and otherwise manage our business;
  * send you newsletters, notices and offers and otherwise correspond with you about products, services, companies and events that we think might interest you;
  * perform research and analysis about your use of or interest in our products and services or the products or services offered by others;
  * develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our Site and other sites, and provide our advertisements to you when you visit other sites;
  * enforce our terms and conditions; and
  * perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

#### THOSE WHO PAY FOR PRODUCTS AND SERVICES

We work with schools, colleges and universities, state and local government agencies, and other institutions to provide programs such as tutoring, test preparation and college admission counseling. Your school, college or university, or other institution may arrange for your participation in these programs and negotiate a special price or trial offer, or purchase (or subsidize) products or services on your behalf. We may share the Personal Information and other information that you provide to us through your participation in these programs, including test scores and the transcripts of on-demand tutoring and on-line class sessions and comments you leave in post-session surveys, with the institution arranging for your access to these programs, or with your parents or guardians. In addition, your school may require us to share such information with others legally entitled to access your academic records, such as your state department of education. If your parents or guardians pay for your account, we may share such information with them. If you use a promotion code at our Site to create an account or add products or services, we may let the source of that promotion code know that you used that code.

#### SERVICE PROVIDERS

We may share your Personal Information with our service providers, including those who help deliver our products and services, help us process transactions, such as charging your credit card when you make purchases, help us market our products and services, and otherwise help us operate our business. These third parties are not authorized by us to use your Personal Information except in connection with providing services to us.

#### SCHOOLS WHICH ARE INTERESTED IN YOU

You may affirmatively agree to the disclosure of your Personal Information to the schools on our Site for their direct marketing purposes by selecting “Request Info” or “Save School” next to the schools or selecting “Select All” from the search results of schools that match your interests. If you select “Save School,” you are also affirmatively agreeing to the disclosure of your Personal Information to other schools that may be interested in you for their direct marketing purposes. If you do not want your Personal Information shared with the schools, do not select the options listed above.

#### LICENSEES AND FRANCHISEES

If you are located outside the United States and Canada, we may share your Personal Information with our licensees and franchisees in your location who may market their products and services to you. If you uncheck “I’d like to receive promotional offers, informative content, product updates and more” under your account settings for The Princeton Review, then we will stop such sharing, but licensees and franchisees who previously received your Personal Information may continue to market their products and services to you.

#### AGGREGATED AND NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION.

We may share non-Personal Information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may also share it with our affiliates and third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our websites and on websites of third parties, and to analyze and report on advertising you see. We may combine Site usage information we collect with other non-Personal Information we obtain from other sources. We may also share aggregated, non-Personal Information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis.

#### LEGALLY COMPELLED DISCLOSURES AND SAFETY

We may disclose user information when compelled to do so by government authorities or otherwise as required or permitted by law, such as to respond to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information to protect the safety of others and when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interfering with our rights or property or the rights or property of others.

#### BUSINESS TRANSFER

If we or all or a portion of our business is acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets.

### Using Caution when Sharing Information with Others

When you contribute to a public area or feature of our Site, such as a chat room, bulletin board, list serve, blog, or wiki, the information that you submit will be made available to the general public. Therefore, we recommend that you do not submit any sensitive information to such areas of our Site, including your full name, home address, phone number, financial information or any other information that would enable other users to locate you or contact you.

Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their Personal Information and should avoid sending Personal Information through insecure email, SMS messaging or similar communications.

When you are on our Site, you may be able to visit or link to other sites not operated by us. We do not control such sites and we are not responsible for the information practices of these sites. This Privacy Policy does not address the information practices of those other websites, and we encourage you to read the posted privacy policies of such sites.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We will update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “Effective Date” at the top of this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check our Site from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy practices, you may use our feedback form or contact us at the following address:

The Princeton Review and Tutor.com  
110 E. 42nd Street, 7th Floor   
New York, NY 10017

### Users Outside of the United States and Canada:

You may request that we delete Personal Information collected from you at the Site by sending an email to [prep@review.com](mailto:prep@review.com) requesting such deletion. Please note that if you are receiving services from us, we will need to keep such information during the course of providing those services to you to communicate with you about them.
